Al Green - Feels Like Christmas, 3
Clarence Carter - Back Door Santa, 3
Shawn Lee's Ping Pong Orchestra - Do You Hear What I Hear, 3
Meditation Singers - What The World Needs For Christmas, 3
Sharon Jones & The Dap-Kings - Ain't No Chimneys In The Projects, 3
The Staple Singers - Who Took The Merry Out Of Christmas, 3
The Chambers Brothers - Merry Christmas, Happy New Year, 4
Vernon Garrett - Merry Christmas, Baby, 2
Vernon Garrett - Christmas Groove, 3
Breakestra - Let The Bells Ring, 3
Albert King - Santa Claus Wants Some Lovin', 4
La Sonora Matancera - Cascabel, 2
