Breakestra - Let The Bells Ring, 3
Vernon Garrett - Merry Christmas, Baby, 4
Jimmy Jules & Nuclear Soul System - Xmas Done Got Funky, 4
Meditation Singers - What The World Needs For Christmas, 4
Shawn Lee's Ping Pong Orchestra - Do You Hear What I Hear, 3
Clarence Carter - Back Door Santa, 2
The Chambers Brothers - Merry Christmas, Happy New Year, 3
Albert King - Santa Claus Wants Some Lovin', 0
The Jive Turkeys - Get Down Santa, 3
